wullo.com 2019-03-04

# Wullo | Privacy

Wullo.com ("Wullo") takes your privacy very seriously and has created this Privacy Policy in order to disclose its use of consumer data collected about you. You may contact Wullo at 3941 S. Bristol St., Suite D337 Santa Ana, CA 92704 or via our contact form. 

By using the Wullo website, or submitting information to us by other means, you are subjecting your information to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers Wullo's treatment of personal information that we collect when you are on Wullo's website and when you use Wullo's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Wullo does not own or control, including websites that we may link to, or to individuals that Wullo does not employ or manage. 

#### Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Wullo may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Wullo will post its updated Privacy Policy on our website located at www.Wullo.com. Wullo encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this site and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to Wullo will be subject to the then current Privacy Policy. 

#### Information Collection

Wullo may collect or receive information about you when you register or submit information, including, but not limited to, username, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, interests, resume and contents thereof, job search history, and any other data included in a submitted profile, resume, or search. Wullo also collects information on the pages you access and other information you may volunteer, such as survey information, ratings, reviews, questions, and answers. Wullo may also record actions taken on our site including, but not limited to, clicks, page views, IP address, and search queries. Wullo may store this information in its equipment or the equipment of third party technology providers. 

#### Use of Information

Wullo, or companies we partner with, may contact you based on your interests such as job postings and career development opportunities. Wullo's site may require you to provide Wullo with contact information (such as your name and email address) and demographic information. Wullo may use your contact information to (a) send you job alerts;(b) create an account;or (c) send you information about Wullo and promotional material from some of Wullo's partners. For the purpose of identifying users and delivering relevant content and advertisements, our partner LiveRamp may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser or a unique ID for your mobile device. To opt-out of LiveRamp cookies, please go [here](http://liveramp.com/opt_out/). Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Wullo may use demographic and/or profile data, including but not limited to search history, to tailor your experience on Wullo's site, show you content that Wullo thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. 

To the extent you upload a resume, Wullo may make the resume and other personal information contained therein available to third parties, including but not limited to employers and search engines. This means that the personal information contained in your resume can be viewed by third parties and you may receive unsolicited contact from third parties unaffiliated with Wullo. Wullo will make reasonable effort to safeguard the use of your personal information by third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Wullo reserves the right to disclose any information as required by law. 

We may use other companies as necessary to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Every effort will be made to safeguard your privacy when it may be accessed by other companies, including but not limited to technology providers;however, Wullo will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. 

Wullo may use your IP address to administer our site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you, your location, and to gather broad demographic information. Nothing shall restrict Wullo from maintaining your data following your termination of your use of Wullo's site. Wullo may delete your user data at Wullo's sole discretion. 

#### Facebook Information Collection and Use

Through our use of Facebook products and services, including but not limited to Facebook Connect and Facebook Platform, we may receive personally identifiable information about you and your friends who are registered on Facebook ("Friend"). We may use this information to customize and improve the services that we provide to you. By visiting Wullo, information that we receive from Facebook about you and your Friends may appear on our site. In addition, if a user visits our site and you are listed as a Friend of that user on Facebook, your information may also appear on our site. You can learn more [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). 

#### Email Communications

Wullo prohibits unsolicited email advertising of its site. 

Wullo respects your email preferences and will never provide your email address to a third party without your permission, except as may be prescribed elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. If you provide us your email address, Wullo may email you job alerts, account notifications, news, offers, surveys, promotions, and other communications. If you do not want to receive particular types of email messages from Wullo, follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email message to notify us of our preferences, or click here. 

#### Children's Privacy

Wullo's site is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. Wullo is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities. Wullo does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor does Wullo target its services or site to children under the age of 13. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 17 ask and receive permission from their parent or guardian prior to using Wullo or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

#### Protect Yourself

Wullo uses automated processes and third party aggregators to collect and present information that has been created by third parties, so we cannot verify the accuracy or legitimacy of all job postings displayed on our site. We strongly encourage you to exercise caution when providing information about yourself to others online, including when you apply for jobs found on Wullo. 

Never provide your social security number, credit card information, bank account details, or unnecessary personal information to a potential employer. Never participate in a financial transaction of any sort with a potential employer. Always be cautious of opportunities that sound too good to be true or require you to act as a financial intermediary, particularly for an overseas person. 

#### Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Wullo may use cookies to keep track of your session and advertising delivery. Wullo or our partners may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save a password associated with a user profile. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use third-party cookies to record information (excluding your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites and directly in emails/communications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on others websites. Our partners may also link the nonpersonal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, hashed version of your email address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. You can learn more [here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). You can opt-out of this type of advertising [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/). 

#### Links to Third Party Sites

The Wullo site may provide links to external websites. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Wullo of those external websites. You acknowledge that Wullo is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Wullo is not responsible for the content of such external websites. Your use of external websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the external websites. 

#### Assignment

If there is a change of control in Wullo's business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise) or if there is an asset sale, the user information, including personal information, could be sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information handling practices as described in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on the site, and you may opt-out of the use of your existing information in a new manner. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of any successors or assigns of Wullo or the assets of Wullo. 

#### Conditions of Use

If you decide to use Wullo's site or services, your use and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us. 

3941 S. Bristol St., Suite D337  
Santa Ana, CA 92704
